foreign
Enchanted Forest at any other time of
year it's an ordinary Woodland but all
who come here for a few weeks are
blessed with the fairy site and you
become witness to a wondrous Realm
the forest floor is absolutely covered
in wildflowers that love to grow in the
chilled earth right after the snow melts
[Music]
thank you
I brought my watercolors in a painting
I've been working on for several weeks
which I finally made into prints for my
shop
something about the forest AIDS my hand
encouraging slow and thoughtful
movements of my paintbrush I could have
stayed there for the entire day but alas
the sun was setting and I had to go home
thank you
foreign
[Music]
a comment that pops up periodically is
that I seem like someone who has refused
to grow up I like to look at the bright
side of things and therefore him
ignoring the harsh realities of
adulthood in a world that is full of
negativity I talk too much about
imagination I read books meant for
children I'm a childish individual it is
an interesting assumption to make I
believe because these videos only
portray a small portion of who I am in
regards to the darkness that is ever
present in the world it is that exact
awareness in my own life experiences
that have driven me to notice the love
and the beauty that exists alongside the
ugliness if I only see cruelty and anger
in the world in a way I become part of
it and continue to perpetuate that
mindset instead of trying to do
something different that has been the
first step to healing and realizing that
my own small existence can still help
make things a bit better
[Music]
foreign
in regards to having childlike interests
I want to encourage other Kindred
Spirits artistic and sensitive souls to
be themselves and not feel shame for
embracing who they are shame can have
such a strong effect but it is also
possible to dismantle with time
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
ly struggle with certain aspects of
adulthood I'm a fairly disorganized
person and find it difficult to stay on
track and be efficient I do much better
if I slow down and focus on one task at
a time at a pace that most work
environments would find unacceptable but
I do the best I can despite these
limitations though I often have thought
that I have no idea how to be an adult
sometimes but perhaps Growing Up by
other standards isn't as important as
growth in general and finding a way to
nurture all the best parts of yourself
I spend most of my time wrapped up in
very mundane and sometimes quite tedious
tasks in regards to my job and future
plans I spend most of the day at work
it's only outside a career chores and
other familial responsibilities that I'm
able to encourage the side of me that
loves to wander dirt roads on Misty
spring mornings we're sitting on the
porch with tea to watch the bats lit
about in the Moonlight
but when I do get some time to myself I
enjoy entertaining my imagination and
storytelling it inspires my art and
offers me great joy
foreign
[Music]
perhaps I am a childlike in a way if
that is what it means to still enjoy
activities I did decades ago it may seem
as if I spend time not doing anything
sometimes just wandering and sitting and
breathing but if that means that being
an adult is spending every second of the
day being productive and busy and
efficient without even a stolen moment
of mindful contemplation or appreciation
of the clouds overhead then yes I'm
proud to be childlike in nature perhaps
I had not grown up but if this is true
then I'm at peace with who I am and I
hope that you can Embrace whatever
lifestyle suits you best as long as
you're living with kindness and a humble
heart I don't see how it can be wrong to
be you
thank you
[Music]
foreign
I was quite happy with how this design
turned out it is by no means perfect I
know there's quite a few things that I
can adjust to make it better in the
future and there's still the other
design I created that I'm hoping to try
once I find a piece of clothing I'm
willing to put a design on so I need to
find that first and then I hope to share
that in a future video but yes I thought
for as a first try it is quite simple to
make you know this design and it is a
very easy process so if you are
interested in screen printing I think
that there's some very easy beginner
kits that you might enjoy trying out
apart from that the topic of this video
of course was something quite close to
my heart and hopefully some words of
encouragement for everyone who is trying
to connect to their more kind of inner
free spirit and their inner childlike
spirit and
um also more sensitive you know people
or people just who enjoy certain things
in life that might not be as commonly
associated with adulthood and being
quite mature I have found it interesting
that there is not always you know a deep
appreciation for more meditative
contemplation and mindfulness in our
daily lives and that it seems sometimes
that that's even connected to being more
uh childlike or frivolous and I I find
that to be interesting and unfortunate
because yes you know spending time with
the wildflowers dancing Outdoors telling
stories enjoying fairy tales these are
all things that I really loved as a
child and a lot of children love
especially you know being fascinated
with nature and finding entertainment in
places that might seem boring and not
valuing productivity and efficiency but
instead valuing the daily experience of
life I I know that that is something
associated with children so much it is
something that I never felt a need to
reject as I got older there of course
were times in my life when I was trying
a lot more to fit in you know whatever
that means because you know there's a
lot of a huge variety of people out
there so there's no reason you need to
try to fit in with any one group seeking
out that excitement and joy in the
little things right I feel like that's a
lot what this channel is all about even
something as simple as an art project
just made my day and it was so exciting
to learn something new even if the final
product did not come out perfectly I do
think it is wonderful you know that we
can continue building this awareness
that slowing down of observing of
appreciating the world like we did maybe
when we were much younger is a quite
healthy and beautiful thing and not
necessarily for everyone but for people
that are perhaps more creative or more
sensitive or just enjoy that lifestyle
it it might be what helps keep them
going and keep them feeling really
positive and joyful enjoy and encourage
your passions and your interests find
things to be excited about if that is
fairy tales if that is children's books
if that is something else altogether
then I think it is just so wonderful to
listen to that inner spirit I think
accepting your true personality and
nurturing your true personality at least
for me was a huge step in appreciating
who I am if we are living with love I
find it hard to find something wrong
with that and as long as we're trying to
do our best to be kind and that is
definitely the inspiration behind so
many of my videos and just I wanted to
reiterate that because I am still get
messages of how my paintings are so
childish or how what I do is boring or
not productive I think it is so crucial
to stay true to your personality and who
you are that doesn't mean don't be open
to change or grow but make sure you're
nurturing and you're getting what you do
need in terms of your own life I wish
you all a wonderful week and that you
continue to nurture what your soul needs
and I'm sending so much love and support
and I will see you very very soon
goodbye
foreign